## **Collin Paradis**

912 West Street, Ludlow, M.A 413-523-2103 CollinParadis7@gmail.com

Highly motivated college graduate with a double major in Computer Information Technology (C.I.T) and Marketing with experience in website design and Information Technology. Enthusiastic about being a part of a team that provides I.T. solutions to an organization.

#### Education

Elms CollegeChicopee, MABachelors of Arts in Computer Information Technology & Bachelors of Arts in MarketingMay 2019Minor in ManagementGPA: 3.74

- NSF STEM Scholarship
- Magna Cum Laude

**Tech Foundry**A fourteen-week comprehensive I.T career development program that focuses on

June 2019

A fourteen-week comprehensive I.I career development program that focuses on building the skills necessary to perform entry technical services. The program puts emphasis on professional development, proper documentation, and gaining real-world experience.

#### Skills

Programming Languages
Operating Systems
Software
Networking

HTML5, CSS, JavaScript, jQuery, PHP, Ajax, C#, Java Windows 7-10, Windows Server 2016, Linux, Mac Office365, Active Directory, ConnectWise, VMware DHCP Client/Server, DNS, E-mail Server

#### Experience

### Freelance Web Designer

Chicopee, MA January 2019 - Present

August 2018 - May 2019

April 2017 - August 2017

## Town of Worthington, Salon Bocage, River Valley Rugby

- Generate and design a website based on the business owners needs and the concepts that they want portrayed.
- Maintain website by updating content, implementing new technology and monitoring performance.

## Elms College Chicopee, MA

### Technical Support Specialist Intern

- Troubleshot issues that faculty and students encounter including problems with performance, software, and peripherals.
- Utilized remote sessions to perform imaging of new computers and installation of software.
- Performed repairs on broken computers to make them functional again.

# Elms College Chicopee, MA Web Designer Intern April 2018 – August 2018

- Collaborated in a team to produce websites using HTML5, WordPress, and Wix that are standard compliant, SEO optimized, and multi-device. Compatible.
- Performed front-end development for websites to improve functionality and user experience using HTML5, CSS, and JavaScript.
- Managed, maintained and updated existing websites for clients.

### Volunteer Activities

Elms College Tech Committee, *Member*C.I.T Computer Lab Monitor, *Volunteer*August 2017 - May 2019

January 2016 - May 2019